sitebeat.com 2012-10-27

# Sitebeat | Privacy Policy

Sitebeat knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn about our privacy policy. By visiting the Sitebeat website, or any related domains, websites, services and pages owned or operated by Sitebeat (collectively the "Site") or using any services made available on the Site ("Service") you are accepting and agreeing to this privacy policy. 

This privacy policy covers Sitebeat's treatment of personal information that you submit and that Sitebeat may gather when you visit or access the Site and/or when you use the Service. Sitebeat is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site, except for content you submit in accordance with the Sitebeat Terms of Use, which shall govern your rights in such content. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Sitebeat does not own or control, or to individuals that Sitebeat does not employ or manage. 

### Information Collected by Sitebeat

We may collect the following types of information from users of our Site or Service: 

  * #### Information You Provide to Us

    * We may receive and store any information you enter on our Site or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to use certain features or aspects of the Site and/or Service. 
    * Registration: In order for you to post information on Sitebeat, such as review or rating for a website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your first name, last name and email address). 
    * User Profile: The User Profile is the area on the Site where we allow you to tell other Sitebeat users about yourself, sites that you have reviewed, how many reviews and other data pertaining to you. To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we allow you to submit additional information such as a photo of yourself, interests you may have, etc. 
    * If your registration or User Profile information changes, or if you no longer desire to have a profile, you may correct, update, or delete such information by emailing our Customer Support at support@Sitebeat.com. 
    * From time-to-time, Sitebeat may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys or contests. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name additional bio-data), and demographic information (such as zip code).  

  * #### Automatic Information

    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit the Site or interact with us. Sitebeat, our service providers and authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Sitebeat cookie information, and the page you requested. Sitebeat uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the Site. 
    * Sitebeat may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. This includes User Profile pages. 

### E-mail Communication

Sitebeat is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, except as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. Sitebeat will communicate with you through email and alerts posted on the Site. Once you have registered with Sitebeat, we may send you promotional information about Sitebeat products and services, unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails about Sitebeat products and services, please send a request to support@Sitebeat.com. Please be aware that you may not opt-out from receiving emails from Sitebeat related to the proper functioning of your account and other administrative matters such as changes to our services, updates to our privacy policy or terms of use, security announcements and other similar messages. 

### Cookies

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages of the Site are visited and by how many people. Sitebeat cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is. 
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Sitebeat's coolest features. 
  * Some of our business partners, like our advertisers, may use cookies on our Site. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. 

### Sharing your Information

Because Sitebeat enables people to discover information about people and their jobs, information about the people who use Sitebeat is an integral part of the Sitebeat experience. Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone without your permission, and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

  * Sitebeat Personnel: Sitebeat personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information in the normal course of Sitebeat business. 
  * We may use third party service providers in our operation of the Site and/or Services. We will only share with our third party service providers information as necessary for the service providers to perform services for the Site and/or Services. 
  * Protection of Sitebeat and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that such release is necessary to comply with a law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or other policies, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Sitebeat, our employees, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 
  * Business Transitions and Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets, or go through a transition such as a merger, sale or acquisition. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. We will notify you by email, posting a notice on the Site, or by some other reasonable means in the event we share or transfer personal information in connection with a business transition or transfer. 
  * User Profile information: Information you submit, and information collected during registration and subsequent visits, such as your full name, interests, picture and other details, may be displayed to other Sitebeat users in your User Profile or other portions of the Site. 
  * API: Sitebeat will allow third parties access to all Sitebeat data this is already publicly available through the Site. Sitebeat will keep private any passwords settings. 
  * Syndication: Sitebeat may allow for the RSS syndication of all of its publicly available content within the Site. 
  * With Your Consent: Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not share your information and will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally submitted or collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information. 

### Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

Sitebeat allows third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Sitebeat does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Sitebeat to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example users interested to Buy a Car) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Sitebeat's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Sitebeat is maintained and dealt with by Sitebeat in accordance with this privacy policy. 

### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, on a notice on the Site, and/or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the Site. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: support@sitebeat.com.
